http://www.ashscotland.org.uk/about-us/privacy-and-cookies-policy/

Electronic cigarettes
Scottish Coalition On Tobacco (SCOT)
Improving Scotland’s Health: 2021 and Beyond Cross-Party Group
2020 (1)back
2020 (1)
Go smoke-free
Reducing families' exposure to second-hand smoke in the home
Go smoke-free
Reducing families' exposure to second-hand smoke in the home
Vacancies
HomeAbout usPrivacy and cookies policy
Privacy and cookies policy
Use of this site
ASH Scotland seeks to ensure that the information published on its website is up to date and accurate. However, the information on the website does not constitute legal or professional advice and ASH Scotland cannot accept any liability for actions arising from its use.
External links
Links to external sites may open in a new window. ASH Scotland cannot be held responsible for the contents of any pages referenced by an external link.
Copyright
The copyright in the material on this ASH Scotland website belongs to ASH Scotland and where appropriate its partners unless otherwise stated. For example, the images on the ASH Scotland site were sourced externally and several reports on our site were also authored by external bodies; these are reproduced on the ASH Scotland website with full permission of the copyright owner. We are happy for other organisations to refer to our website in their own website, and to create hypertext links as appropriate, provided ASH Scotland is acknowledged . We are also happy for you to reproduce and distribute material from our website, for non-commercial purposes only, providing that ASH Scotland is clearly stated as the source. If in doubt or for further information please contact ASH Scotland and we will be happy to advise you.
Personal data
ASH Scotland has an ‘opt-in only’ communication policy. This means that we will only send communications to those that have explicitly stated that they are happy for us to do so via their preferred channel.  Any personal data collected through this website will be treated as confidential in line with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998.   We have also updated our privacy policy in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation.
Bulletin mailing listsWe use a third party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our e-newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies including clear gifs to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see Mailchimp privacy policy.BlogsOur blog is hosted by Medium:  Medium's privacy policy is here.Campaign micrositesWe use a third party service, WordPress.com, to publish our microsites: IMPACT and notafavour and befree. These sites are hosted at WordPress.com, which is run by Automattic Inc. We use a standard WordPress service to collect anonymous information about users' activity on the site, for example the number of users viewing pages on the site, to monitor and report on the effectiveness of the site and help us improve it. WordPress requires visitors that want to post a comment to enter a name and email address. For more information about how WordPress processes data, please see Automattic's privacy noticeOnline learning coursesASH Scotland's e-learning courses are hosted on Moodle.  Moodle has a Privacy notice which all logged-in users must agree to in order to proceed further on the siteTwitterWe use Tweetdeck to manage our Twitter accounts. If you send us a private or direct message via social media the message may be stored by Twitter. It will not be shared with any other organisations.  For further information please see Twitter's privacy policy.
CookiesCookies are information packets sent by web servers to web browsers, and stored by the web browsers.  The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables a web server to identify and track web browsers.
There are two main kinds of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser, whereas persistent cookies remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach their expiry date.ASH Scotland uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: www.google.com/privacypolicy.htmlRefusing cookiesMost browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies.
In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.
In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies settings by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”.For other browsers visit www.aboutcookies.org
Blocking cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of some websites.
About us
Our organisational strategy 2018 to 2021
Annual report
Our people
Excluding the tobacco industry
Contact us
SitemapAccessibilityPrivacy and cookies policyFind us
Action on Smoking & Health (Scotland) (ASH Scotland) is a registered Scottish charity (SC 010412) and a company limited by guarantee(Scottish company no 141711). The registered office is 8 Frederick Street, Edinburgh EH2 2HB.
ASH Scotland acknowledges with thanks the support of the British Heart Foundation and the Scottish Government in developing our website.
© 2020 ASH Scotland
